[
    {
        "question": "1 x 1 = ?",
        "choice1": "3",
        "choice2": "5",
        "choice3": "1",
        "choice4": "2",
        "answer": 3
    },

    {
        "question": "2 x 1 = ?",
        "choice1": "7",
        "choice2": "2",
        "choice3": "1",
        "choice4": "4",
        "answer": 2
    },

    {
        "question": "3 x 1 = ?",
        "choice1": "3",
        "choice2": "4",
        "choice3": "2",
        "choice4": "9",
        "answer": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "4 x 1 = ?",
        "choice1": "3",
        "choice2": "4",
        "choice3": "8",
        "choice4": "6",
        "answer": 2
    },

    {
        "question": "5 x 1 = ?",
        "choice1": "5",
        "choice2": "4",
        "choice3": "1",
        "choice4": "7",
        "answer": 1
    },

    {
        "question": "6 x 1 = ?",
        "choice1": "5",
        "choice2": "9",
        "choice3": "6",
        "choice4": "7",
        "answer": 3
    },

    {
        "question": "7 x 1 = ?",
        "choice1": "1",
        "choice2": "3",
        "choice3": "4",
        "choice4": "7",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "8 x 1 = ?",
        "choice1": "3",
        "choice2": "8",
        "choice3": "4",
        "choice4": "6",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "9 x 1 = ?",
        "choice1": "9",
        "choice2": "8",
        "choice3": "10",
        "choice4": "1",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "10 x 1 = ?",
        "choice1": "9",
        "choice2": "8",
        "choice3": "10",
        "choice4": "1",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "11 x 1 = ?",
        "choice1": "11",
        "choice2": "8",
        "choice3": "3",
        "choice4": "7",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "12 x 1 = ?",
        "choice1": "11",
        "choice2": "10",
        "choice3": "12",
        "choice4": "7",
        "answer": 3
    }
    {
        "question": "1 x 2 = ?",
        "choice1": "2",
        "choice2": "10",
        "choice3": "4",
        "choice4": "1",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "2 x 2 = ?",
        "choice1": "3",
        "choice2": "2",
        "choice3": "4",
        "choice4": "6",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "3 x 2 = ?",
        "choice1": "4",
        "choice2": "6",
        "choice3": "3",
        "choice4": "8",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "4 x 2 = ?",
        "choice1": "4",
        "choice2": "2",
        "choice3": "8",
        "choice4": "6",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "5 x 2 = ?",
        "choice1": "12",
        "choice2": "10",
        "choice3": "8",
        "choice4": "5",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "6 x 2 = ?",
        "choice1": "14",
        "choice2": "8",
        "choice3": "12",
        "choice4": "6",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "7 x 2 = ?",
        "choice1": "14",
        "choice2": "10",
        "choice3": "12",
        "choice4": "16",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "8 x 2 = ?",
        "choice1": "12",
        "choice2": "16",
        "choice3": "18",
        "choice4": "8",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "9 x 2 = ?",
        "choice1": "14",
        "choice2": "16",
        "choice3": "12",
        "choice4": "18",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "10 x 2 = ?",
        "choice1": "16",
        "choice2": "20",
        "choice3": "18",
        "choice4": "10",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "11 x 2 = ?",
        "choice1": "20",
        "choice2": "10",
        "choice3": "22",
        "choice4": "18",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "12 x 2 = ?",
        "choice1": "16",
        "choice2": "24",
        "choice3": "12",
        "choice4": "22",
        "answer": 2
    }
]
